nzpost.co.nz 2006-06-16

# Privacy Statement

Any personal information collected by New Zealand Post in connection with this website will be held for the purpose of linking you with career opportunities at New Zealand Post.

All personal information and documentation will be held securely by New Zealand Post in compliance with the Privacy Act 1993. Personal information and documentation collected and held may include resumes, academic transcripts, interview notes, reference information and test results. It will primarily be stored electronically on New Zealand Post's candidate database.

You may request removal of your personal information at any time. Otherwise, it will be kept in the New Zealand Post Recruitment Centre for six months before being destroyed, unless you have an application still in progress.

While your personal information is on New Zealand Post's candidate database, the following rules apply:

  * You will be responsible for maintaining your profile and ensuring that the information held is correct and up to date. You may view and amend your personal information at any time. 
  * You can request access to all and any information held about you by New Zealand Post and request correction of that information. The request must be in writing to New Zealand Post Recruitment Centre, Private Bag 39990, Wellington, New Zealand. 
  * New Zealand Post's Recruitment Centre may provide information about you, whether provided by you or a third party nominated by you for that purpose, to a prospective New Zealand Post Manager after having first briefed you on the vacancy and you have authorised us to do so. 
  * New Zealand Post's Recruitment Centre will only contact and collect personal information from any former employer or other person you have nominated as a referee if you have specifically authorised us to do so. 
  * After you accept an offer of employment with New Zealand Post, your information will become part of New Zealand Post's employee records. This information will be held in confidence and not disclosed to anyone without your consent. 
  * We may use a trusted third party to help us process, administer and store your information, however it will be protected by strict confidentiality agreements. 

For additional information, please contact the Recruitment Centre at New Zealand Post either by emailing [careers@nzpost.co.nz](mailto:careers@nzpost.co.nz) or by calling 0800 202 204.
